// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {numb: 1,
    question: "The Spanish Steps are in which city?",
    answer: "Rome",
    options: [
      "Rome",
      "Madrid",
      "Valencia",
      "Barcelona"]},
    {numb: 2,
    question: "Which European country has the most World Heritage sites?",
    answer: "Italy",
    options: [
      "Ukraine",
      "Estonia",
      "Germany",
      "Italy"]},
    {numb: 3,
    question: "Which capital city is the furthest north in the world?",
    answer: "Reykjavik",
    options: [
      "Reykjavik",
      "Helsinki",
      "Tallinn",
      "Oslo"]},
    {numb: 4,
    question: "If you were cruising in Halong Bay, you would be in what country?",
    answer: "Vietnam",
    options: [
      "Vietnam",
      "Korea",
      "Japan",
      "Bali"]},
    {numb: 5,
    question: "What is the most photographed landmark in Australia?",
    answer: "Sydney Opera House",
    options: [
      "Sydney Opera House",
      "Time Squere",
      "Bell tower",
      "Taj Mahal"]},
   {numb: 6,
    question: "Which Italian landmark dates back to 70AD?",
    answer: "The Colosseum in Rome",
    options: [
      "The Colosseum in Milan",
      "Vatican",
      "The Colosseum in Rome",
      "Bolivia"]},
	{numb: 7,
    question: "Which Greek God has been immortalised in a statue that you can visit in Olympia?",
    answer: "Zeus",
    options: [
      "Thor",
      "Zeus",
      "Milana",
      "Poseidon"]},
	  {numb: 8,
    question: "What is the average percentage of salt in the Dead Sea?",
    answer: "33%",
    options: [
      "33%",
      "21%",
      "78%",
      "30%"]},
	  {numb: 9,
    question: "What percentage of the earth is water?",
    answer: "71%",
    options: [
      "31%",
      "81%",
      "91%",
      "71%"]},
	  {numb: 10,
    question: "In miles, how long is the Eurotunnel?",
    answer: "31.4 miles",
    options: [
      "30 miles",
      "20 miles",
      "31.4 miles",
      "60 miles"]},
	  {numb: 11,
    question: "What is the nickname for the clock at the end of the Palace of Westminster?",
    answer: " Big Ben ",
    options: [
      "Ben",
      "Bog Bom",
      " Big Ben ",
      "Lorry"]},
	  {numb: 12,
    question: "What is the popular Mexican dish of meat, rice, vegetables, beans and a selection of condiments wrapped in a tortilla called?",
    answer: "Burrito",
    options: [
      "Burrito",
      "Hallumi",
      "Chips",
      "Taco"]},
	  {numb: 13,
    question: "What is Tom Yum Goong?.",
    answer: "A spicy shrimp soup, and popular Thai dish.",
    options: [
      "cheese from Greece",
      "Sause in Portugal",
      "Paella from Spain",
      "Kind of suchi in Japan"]},
	  {numb: 14,
    question: "What is Я ?",
    answer: "last letter in Russian alphabet",
    options: [
      "last letter in Serbian-Croation alphabet",
      "it is R",
      "last letter in Russian alphabet",
      "none"]},
	  {numb: 15,
    question: "Which famous Michelangelo statue is in the Italian city of Florence?",
    answer: "Statue of David",
    options: [
      "Big Ben",
      "Statue of David",
      "Adam",
      "Bali"]},
	  {numb: 16,
    question: "What is the national dish of Hungary?",
    answer: " Gulyás (Goulash)",
    options: [
      "Gulyás (Goulash)",
      "Dumplings",
      "Fish and Chips",
      "Borscht"]},
	  {numb: 17,
    question: "In which year did British Airways begin?",
    answer: "1919",
    options: [
      "1919",
      "1819",
      "1950",
      "680"]},
	  {numb: 18,
    question: "The Temple of the Emerald Buddha and The Grand Palace can be found in which Asian capital?",
    answer: "Bangkok in Thailand",
    options: [
      "Bangkok in South Korea",
      "Kinogo in Latvia",
      "Bangkok in Thailand",
      "Bali in Indonesia"]},
	  {numb: 19,
    question: "SeaWorld, Universal Studios and Walt Disney World are all theme parks in which Florida city?",
    answer: "Orlando",
    options: [
      "Chicago",
      "Tallinn",
      "Orlando",
      "New York",]},
	  {numb: 20,
    question: "What is the capital city of Cuba?",
    answer: "Havana",
    options: [
      "Havana",
      "Mexico city",
      "Rome",
      "Vancuver",]},
];